<resources>
    <string name="app_name"> Uttrakhand Tourism</string>

    <string name="ykedarnath">\n<b>About</b>\nKedarnath Dham is an uphill trek for about 22 kilometers from Gauri Kund. The Kedarnath Dham is known to be one of the five spots believed to be where Lord Shiva resides. In the Vedas and Puranas, the word ‘Kedar’ refers to Lord Shiva. Kedarnath, as per holy belief and sacredness, is known to be the land of Lord Shiva, where Lord still resides in the form of Linga. It is also the highest located jyotirlinga. The temple is an old stone edifice located on the shores of Mandakini River. Situated in the Rudraprayag district of Uttarakhand, Kedarnath is the most remote pilgrimage spot in the yatra.</string>

    <string name="yabout">\n<b>About</b>\nYamunotri is where the second most holy of river of India, the River Yamuna, takesbirth. It is named after Goddess Yamuna. Situated in the Uttarkashi district of Uttarakhand, Yamunotri Dhamis the first stop inthe pilgrimage. It is believed that bathing in its water cleanses all sins and protects from untimely and painful death. The shrine of Yamunotri is believed to be built in1839 by the king of Tehri, Naresh Sudarshan Shah. There are many hot water springs near the temple; Surya Kund is the most important among them.</string>

    <string name="gabout">\n<b>About</b>\nGangotri Dham is dedicated to Goddess Ganga, who is said to have descended on earth to absolve the sins of human kind. The river originates at Gaumukh from the Gangotri glacier which is some 18 km from the town of Gangotri. Situated in Uttarkashi district of Uttarakhand, the original temple of Gangotri was built by by Amar Singh Thapa, a Gurkha general, in the early 19th century. Some popular religious locations like the Bhagirath Shila and the Pandava Gufa are also present close to the Gangotri Dham.</string>

    <string name="aboutrisikesh">\n<b>About</b>\n  Rishikesh is a tehsil located in Uttarakhand’s Tehri Garhwal region right on the banks of the holiest of Indian rivers, the Ganges. This ancient city has several mythological and religious legends associated with Lord Vishnu, Lord Bharat, and various prominent sages and is said to have been established in the 9th-century AD by Adi Shankaracharya. The scenic beauty of Rishikesh is due to its location at the foot hills of the lofty Garhwal Himalayas is accentuated by the mighty Ganges cutting right through the city. The city is synonymous with its grand temples, rituals, architectural marvels and yoga ashrams.</string>

    <string name="aboutmussoorie">\n<b>About</b>\n Located in close proximity to Dehradun, this beautiful hill station is one of the most amazing places to visit in Uttarakhand. Located in the midst of Garhwal Himalayan ranges, Mussoorie enjoys a wonderful weather all the year round. Some of the must- visit places in Mussoorie are Kempty Falls, Lal Tibba and The Mall. Home to different hills, lakes, and temples, this place derives its name from a shrub known as Mansoor, which is found here in large quantities.</string>

    <string name="aboutdehradun">\n<b>About</b>\n Surrounded by the breathtaking Doon valley, Dehradun is a well-known hill station, which never fails to entice travelers, be it families, couples or backpackers. This place is also renowned for marvelous architectural display. Lying at the foothills of the Himalayas, Dehradun which is the capital of Uttarakhand is known for its beautiful climate and the lovely landscapes it encompasses. One of the most astonishing facts about this place however, is that it is also one of the most important education hubs in the whole of India.</string>

    <string name="aboutnainital">\n<b>About</b>\n Nainital, the lake city of India comes in the list of top 10 best tourist destinations to visit in Uttarakhand in India. The scenic natural splendor, the pleasant weather, the colorful markets, delicious cuisines and lofty Himalayan mountains will never cease to elevate your soul. It is a very popular religious tourist destination as Naina Devi-Temple surrounded with lofty Himalayan mountains in the backdrop will enchant your spirit. Moreover, Nainital is also a very sceni chill station to enjoy throughout the year. You will witness the seven hills known as Sapta- Shring.</string>

    <string name="dehradunhotel">Hotel : Sarovar Portico</string>
    <string name="lorem">Lorea</string>


    <string name="uttkhndabout">Uttrakhand also known as uttranchal. Due to religious significance and numours hindu temples it is offen refered to as "Dev-Bhumi" thats is Land of Gods.</string>

    <string name="aboutBadrinath">Badrinath is a town and nagar panchayat in Chamoli district in the state of Uttarakhand, India. A Hindu holy place, it is one of the four sites in India\'s Char Dham pilgrimage and is also part of India Chota Char Dham pilgrimage circuit. Badrinath or Badrinarayana Temple is a Hindu temple dedicated to Vishnu. The temple is also one of the 108 Divya Desams dedicated to Vishnu - holy shrines for Vaishnavas - who is worshipped as Badrinath</string>
    <string name="aboutkedarnathhotel"><b>About Phulwari Resort Sitapur (Kedarnath): </b>
Phulwari Resort Sitapur (Kedarnath) is a great option for travellers looking out for homestay in Kedarnath. It is located in Sonaprayag.This Homestay stands out as one of the highly recommended homestay in Kedarnath and is recommended by 100% of our guests. Homestay is rated 5.0 out of 5, which is considered as excellent.From all the Budget hotels in Kedarnath, Phulwari Resort Sitapur (Kedarnath) is very much popular among the tourists. </string>
</resources>